admagnet.com 2012-09-19

# Privacy Policy | AD MAGNET

Digital Media Private Limited ("Ad-Magnet") is a technology-enabled ad-network services Company whose clients and customers include both online advertisers ("Advertisers") and Internet content sites ("Publishers"). We deliver innovative products and services designed to: 

  * Enable Advertisers to better reach their target audiences; and
  * Enable Publishers to support, grow and monetize their websites through the sale of advertisements.

(collectively referred to as the ‘Services’)  
This Privacy Policy is as per the Indian Information Technology Act, 2000 and the Information Technology (Reasonable security and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011 prescribed thereunder, (“Applicable Law”) that is intended to provide consumers with clear and complete information about the consumer data and information that we collect in connection with our Services and the way that data and information is stored and used by our Company. 

Information We Collect 

Non-Personal Information Collected by our Services. We deliver advertisements from hundreds of Advertisers across a large number of Publisher websites, which are a part of our ad-network. When you visit one of the Publisher websites in our network, our automated system may collect "click stream data" related to your visit to the website. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as your IP address, Operating System details, Browser details, the date and time at which those pages were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those Web pages. Technologies used to collect this click stream data, include cookies and Web beacons.   
In order to improve performance, we augment our click stream data with non-personally-identifiable behavioral and demographic data from Publishers and other partners. This anonymous data may include such things as zip code, age, gender and income range but shall not include any kind of Sensitive Personal Data or Information (as defined under Applicable Law), which the Publisher may collect on its website.   
We utilize the non-personal information, described above to better customize the sort of advertisements you see. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data in order to identify large audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to the most relevant Internet audience. We store the information collected in log files, and log files are retained in our systems for a reasonable period of time. Anonymous data stored in our log files, that associates the log data to a particular computer include IP address and cookie ID. We purge the IP address and irreversibly obfuscate the cookie ID from our log files as soon as we believe this information is no longer required by us. 

Consumer Choice - Opting Out of Receiving Cookies 

We use technology which includes cookies and web beacons in the delivery of our Services. We believe that the use of these tools enables us to provide users with a more meaningful web experience. You may adjust your computer's web browser settings to refuse all cookies. However, please note that because cookies are widely used, disabling the use of cookies in your web browser may interfere with full use of various websites. 

You may Opt out of receiving Ad Magnet cookies by [](http://n.admagnet.net/panda/www/delivery/optout.php)  
You can also Opt out of receiving cookies from Ad Magnet by 

You may Opt in of receiving Ad Magnet cookies by [](http://n.admagnet.net/panda/www/delivery/optin.php)  
You can also Opt in of receiving cookies from Ad Magnet by 

Through this opt-out procedure, your computer will request an "opt-out cookie" ID tag that will prevent your anonymous data from being matched to your computer and thereby prevent us from using that data to deliver targeted advertising or other content to your computer's browser. Please note that this opt-out process will erase the cookie ID associated with your computer but not the cookie itself - the cookie itself must remain on your computer in order for us to recognize you as an opt-out user. This means that if you use multiple computers or multiple browsers you will need to opt out of receiving cookies on each computer and for each browser. Also, if you change computers or delete cookies from your computer you will need to repeat this opt-out process.  
Personal Information Collected by our Service helps marketers reach potential customers who are interested in receiving information about their products or services. Personal Information means “any information that relates to a natural person, which either directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available is capable of identifying a user) or sensitive personal data or information”. In response to a marketer's advertisement, you may choose to provide personal data or information such as your name, address, telephone number and/or email address.  
We will not merge any of this personal data or information with any non-personally identifiable information collected by our systems and will not use this personal data or information in any way that is not authorized by the marketer for whom it is collected. In addition, we keep this data in a separate database to preserve our guarantee that advertisements are delivered only through the utilization of anonymous consumer data.  
Personal Information Collected Through Our Corporate Website: You may also provide us with personal data or information (such as your name, email address, physical address or telephone number) when you elect to contact us about this Privacy Policy or any other customer-service related matter. We will only utilize such personal data or information for the purpose of responding to your inquiry. However, we do reserve the right to retain an archival record of all such correspondence.  
We reserve the right to disclose personal data or information you have disclosed to us in response to any judicial process or court order or to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation of matters related to public safety, as permitted by Applicable Law. In addition, your non-personal information and your personal data or information shall be shared, without obtaining prior consent from you, with Government agencies mandated under the Applicable Law to obtain information for the purpose of verification of identity, or to prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences. 

International Transfers of Information:

Sensitive Personal data or information collected by us may be transferred to any other country for processing/storing or providing you with our Services. You acknowledge and agree that personal data or information you provide to us may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. Providing such information will constitute your consent to any such transfer. 

Information Security:

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to, destruction or disclosure of data. This includes undertaking necessary physical, electronic and management activities required to protect data integrity, access and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential and is not made generally available to the public. Our servers are protected by firewalls and are located in secure data facilities to further increase security. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data or information at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

Transfer of Information Upon Change of Control: 

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset, purchase or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all data (including any personal data or information) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party.

Changes to this Privacy Policy:

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on this page. The date on which the current Privacy Policy was posted will always be noted at the top of this page. Any change we make to our Privacy Policy will be made in compliance with Applicable Law.

Correspondence:

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including your email address. This relates to your correspondence with us only - we do not gather users' email addresses as part of our online advertising business. 

Questions and Comments:

Questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to  or mailed to: [policy@admagnet.com ](mailto:policy@admagnet.com%C2%A0)
